

Dr. Matías Javier MICHELETTO

Bahía Blanca - Argentina +54 9 291 4380079 matiasmicheletto@gmail.com

website in linkedin

SUMMARY

After obtaining my Electronic Engineering degree, I started working as PhD candidate under a CONICET intern scholarship where acquired skills and experience in data science, software and hardware development applied to a wide variety of applications and collaborating with researchers from different disciplines. I have worked as teaching assistant and have published 5+ articles in international journals and participated in 15+ national and international conferences related to technology, education and engineering.

EDUCATION _

Universidad Nacional del Sur

2016-2021

PhD Engineering

- Thesis title: "Development of Computer Systems for Supporting Agricultural Work in the Southwest of the Buenos Aires Province". Thesis grade: 10/10.
- · Advisors: Dr. Rodrigo M. Santos and Dr. Juan A. Galantini.

Universidad Nacional del Sur

2007-2016

B.S. ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING

• GPA: 8.17/10. Awarded with four undergraduate student scholarships and a one-year internship.

EXPERIENCE _

CAPP MOBILE BB S.R.L.

2019

FRONT-END SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

 Collaboration in the design and implementation of the CAPP mobile application, backoffice, admin panel and shop website.

NEUFITECH S.R.L. 2017-2019

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER AND IOT ENGINEER

 Design and implementation of a PWA platform. Desing and implementation of IoT devices as interfaces for disabled people.

Universidad Nacional del Sur

2016-2020

TEACHING ASSISTANT

• Digital electronic courses for engineering students.

SKILLS

Experienced: HTML+JS+CSS | C++ | Matlab **Familiar:** Python | SQL | Java PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES DATA SCIENCE TOOLS & LIBRARIES Jupyter | Matplotplib | Numpy | Pandas | Scikit-learn React|S | Angular 1 | Bootstrap | Materialize | Framework7 | Firebase | Heroku WEB FRAMEWORKS AND TOOLS MOBILE DEVELOPMENT Apache Cordova | React Native **IOT AND EMBEDDED SYSTEMS** Arduino | NodeMCU | Raspberry

EXTRA ____

- Awarded 2nd place "Agroton 2018" (24hr innovation contest).
- Teaching and coaching habilities acquired through 5+ years experience in college's engineering courses.
- · Creative problem solver, detailed and meticulous.